

- danielafrolich@gmail.com
- +46735121251
- in linkedin.com/in/danielafrolich
- www.danielafrolich.com

INTERACTION DESIGNER / FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I am a driven and ambitious person that wants to combine my interest's IT and design to create products and services with great user experience. I have experience of user-centered design and mobile / front-end development from work, school and personal projects.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2020

MSc Interaction Design & Technologies - Chalmers University of Technology The program teaches us as students to design and create interactive digital products. It has a user-centric approach. We learn to combine IT and design to create products that are not only efficient but also have great user experience. I have read courses covering design and development of mobile and web applications.

Spring 2019

MSc Digital Media Engineering - Technical University of Denmark I took an exchange semester in Copenhagen to read courses in interaction design and front-end development. This was a great chance to further develop my technical skills in an international environment.

2015 - 2018

BSc Industrial Design Engineering - Chalmers University of Technology
The program focuses on user-centered design and innovation. We learn how
to efficiently communicate ideas from low-fi sketching to presentable high-fi
prototypes. I developed an interest for UX and digital design during this
time.

Spring 2018

Bachelor Thesis Industrial Design Engineering - Volvo Trucks
We created a concept for the digital interface of Volvos future electric trucks.
The focus of the project was energy visualization. The thesis involved user research, ideation, prototyping and usability testing. One idea was examined for a patent by Volvo and the project received the highest grade.



- danielafrolich@gmail.com
- +46735121251
- in linkedin.com/in/danielafrolich
- www.danielafrolich.com

EXPERIENCE

June 2019
- Present

Interaction designer & front-end developer - Appva

A team of developers and I redesigned Appva's back office system, according to their guidelines and brand identity. Usability tests showed that my design improved the productivity and user experience of the system. We worked according to agile methodologies and used Git for version control. I am currently working part-time with designing an interface for a AI service.

Summers 2016 - 2018

Traffic Planner - Renova

I worked in various systems to manage the traffic planning for the recycling cars. I got experience of working in teams and the same time being self-driven and having a responsibility from this position.

2014 - 2015

Cash & Store Assistant - Willys

I worked as a cashier and in the store with display and packaging.

2013 - 2014

Work Abroad - PAUL Café London

I learned about customer service and further developed my English skills.

2012 - 2013

Economy Assistant - Nordea

My tasks were working in systems like SAP to manage accounts and handling invoices. The position required that I was structured and accurate.

SKILLS

Coding	Prototyping	UX methods	Languages
Android development	Figma / Sketch	Usability tests	Swedish - native
HTML & CSS / SASS	Photoshop	User research	English - fluent
Javascript/JQuery	Illustrator	Story mapping	French - basic
Git	Low-fi prototyping	Affinity diagrams	

OTHER

I was a member of the student divisions' future career union, TDJobb, where I designed posters and other promotional material. I have a class B driver's license.